WILLIAM MUIJS

Frontend Developer

+31685129807

Remote

williammuys@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/william-muijs

₾ 05-01-1994

PROFILE

I am an enthusiastic and creative frontend developer with 3+ years of experience at various companies and projects. The most important things in my professional life are continuous improvement of knowledge and quality of work. I have a great passion for designing and developing complex digital environments.

I also have a great passion for travel and, therefore, it is my intention to work fully remote for most of the year.

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer - Freelance

Itonomy

08-2021 - 09-2021

Utrecht

Code audit for a big player in Dutch e-commerce. My responsibility was to provide an extensive audit report containing analyses of identified problems, and suggestions for improving their current Angular PWA.

Frontend Developer

Incentro

02-2018 - 08-2021

Utrecht

Web application development with the Alfresco Digital Business Platform with experience at various companies and projects. Alfresco is a content management system used to manage the lifecycle of records/documents from capture through retention to final destruction.

PROJECTS (VIA INCENTRO)

Ministerie van Defensie

1 05-2020 - 07-2021

From scratch implementation of the Alfresco Digital Business Platform with a web application and RESTful microservices to manage the lifecycle of records/documents from capture through retention to final destruction.

My responsibilities included creating a web application from scratch, coaching and mentoring colleagues in the area of frontend development, development of (BPMN) process logic and the development of REST APIs with custom business logic.

 Angular 2+, TypeScript, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SCSS, RxJS, Jasmine, Karma, Cypress, Java, Spring, SQL, BPMN, Git and more



SKILLS

Angular	Java	Spring
TypeScri	pt J	avaScript
HTML	CSS	SCSS
RxJS	NgRx	NPM
Cypress	Jasmine	
Karma		

EDUCATION

Master's Degree, Business Information Management

Erasmus University Rotterdam

<u>12-2017</u> 09-2016 - 12-2017

Bachelor's Degree, International Business Administration

University of Twente

09-2012 - 12-2015

VWO, Economics and Society

Guido de Brès

2006 - 2012

APS Group

04-2020

Built a successful proof-of-concept web application to demo the functionalities of the Alfresco Digital Business Platform.

 Angular 2+, TypeScript, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SCSS, RxJS, BPMN, Git, Trello

Gemeente Rotterdam



12-2018 - 12-2019

From scratch implementation of the Alfresco Digital Business Platform with a web application and RESTful microservices to manage the lifecycle of records/documents from capture through retention to final destruction.

My responsibilities included creating a web application from scratch, development of (BPMN) process logic and the development of REST APIs with custom business logic.

• Angular 2+, TypeScript, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, SCSS, RxJS, Java, Spring, SQL, BPMN, Git and more

C. Steinweg Group



10-2018 - 11-2018

Worked on a content migration tool for an Alfresco Content Services instance.

· Java, Git

Saxion University of Applied Sciences



7 07-2018 - 08-2018

Added features to an existing web application for the (lifecycle) management of school exams using Alfresco Content Services.

· Angular 2+, HTML, TypeScript, CSS, SCSS, RxJS, Git

Gemeente Zaanstad



1 04-2018 - 06-2018

Implementation of Alfresco Content Services plus the development of custom business logic.

· Java, JavaScript, Git

STUDY ABROAD

Honors Business Administration

Ivey Business School at **Western University**



09-2017 - 12-2017

Exchange semester in London, Ontario, Canada

Business Management and Administration

Universidad Pablo de Olavide



1 09-2014 - 01-2015

Exchange semester in Seville, Spain

LANGUAGES

Dutch





English Spanish



OTHER



Sabbaticals

In 2020 I took a 3 month sabbatical during which I traveled in a few countries in South America.

In 2015-2016, between my bachelor's and master's, I worked and traveled in Australia and Southeast Asia for a total of 8 months.